厄尔  能借你的报纸看吗
Earl, can I borrow your paper?
我想看看星座运势表
I want to check my horoscope
看看我未来还是不是个"婊"
to see if I'll still be a whore in the future.
先念谁的星座呢
All right, who wants to go first?
我的  我的  我的[上我]
Ooh, do me. Do me. Do me.
你能不能别每天晚上
Can we have one night at the diner
都在餐厅里对女人喊出这句话啊
that doesn't end with you yelling that at a woman?
好吧  先念我的
All right, I'll go.
"双子座  双生子"
"Gemini, the twins,"
这"两娃"都过得挺好  下一个
And they're both doing fine, so let's move on.
阿憨  你是什么星座
Han, what sign are you?
我猜是《四十岁老处男》座
I'm guessing the 40-year-old Virgo.
麦克斯  你哪需要星座运势表
Max, you don't need that paper.
本大仙告诉你未来如何
I'll tell you what's in your future--
用我当你的推荐人去墨西哥餐馆找工作
using my name as a reference at Chipotle.
你们真信这些狗屁玩意吗
You guys really believe in that crap?
上面都是写你们想听的
They just tell you what you want to hear.
"你会大富大贵  你会名扬四海"
"You will be rich. You will be famous."
你觉得如果有报纸写
You'd think I'd buy a newspaper if it said,
"你会是75岁的收银员"  我会买吗
"You will be a 75-year-old cashier"?
准备好开店了吗
Okay, ready to open?
过去从来没有  未来也不会有
Never have been, never will be.
咱们开门吧
Let's do this.
等等
Wait.
我们得念一下我们的开店宣誓
We have to do our business affirmation.
求你了  老天爷  别让我们横死店里
Please, God, don't let us be murdered in here.
好了  开门接客吧
All right, let's open 'em up.
-我勒个去  -麦克斯
- Oh, hell no. - Max.
等会  我还没感叹完
Hang on. I wasn't done.
我勒个大去哦
Oh, hell no!
她在"毛线轰炸"那自行车
Oh, she's yarn-bombing that bike.
好有奇思妙想  好新鲜
It's whimsical. It's new.
好蠢
It's stupid.
喷漆涂鸦  我能理解
Graffiti, I get.
比如看到墙上喷了"去死吧  贱人"
I see, "die, bitch. Die," on a wall,
我就觉得"好吧  这位先生很想发泄心中不快"
I think, "okay, this gentleman wanted to get that off his chest."
但这个毛线玩意可悲透了
But this yarn-ival is pathetic.
喂  毛线妞
Yo, yarnie.
人家是有名字的
I have a name.
我叫滚娘
It's Guinevere.
没错  果然人如其名
Yep, that checks out.
你这是在搞什么
What's happening over here?
你为什么要侵犯可怜的小车车
Why are you molesting that poor bike?
我是在美化城市
I am beautifying the city
用我活力十足的大作慢慢改善市容
one living, glorious work of art at a time.
随时欢迎你们给点小费哦
And tips are always appreciated.
给你个建议[小费]
Here's a tip:
滚回学校好好读书
Go back to school and learn a trade
在花完你爹的钱之前学门手艺
before daddy's money runs out.
我从来...
Well, I never--
没有工作过任何一天吗  我们知道
worked a day in your life, we know.
你觉得这也算艺术品吗
You think this is artwork?
一个加菲猫马克杯才算艺术品  宝贝
Artwork is a Garfield mug, sweetheart.
如果你有个加菲猫躺吊床上说
You got Garfield in a hammock, saying,
"我不是过胖  只是过于不够高大"
"I'm not overweight. I'm under-tall,"
老娘立刻在这里给你盖个美术馆
I'll build you a gallery right here.
您还是请走吧
Look, you should move on.
我的朋友不想你...
My friend doesn't want you--
我该怎么说呢
How shall I put this?
在我们店门口拉这么大一泡"毛线"
Taking a giant knit in front of our shop.
这有啥不对  那台自行车又不是你们的
What is the problem? It is not even your bike.
都被锁在那边大概有四个月了吧
It's been chained here for, like, four months.
是咩
Oh, yeah?
或许它就是我们的
Maybe it is our bike,
我们骑它去外送小蛋糕
and we use it for deliveries
以及用它给自行车宅下套
and to trap nerds.
慢走不送  大麻妞
Peace out, ganja beer,
不然我织个三尺毛绫  吊死你
before I knit you a noose.
麦克斯  刚才的主意真棒
Max, that was a great idea.
哪个  叫她滚回去读书吗
What, that she go back to school?
本来就是嘛
I know.
好歹读个夜校之类的吧
At least a couple night classes, right?
认识一些正常人
Get around some people.
她早没救了  不用鸟她
She's a lost cause. Let's move on.
我是说我们做外送
I'm talking about us doing deliveries.
为什么我们从不外送[让人满意]呢
Why do we never deliver?
别拖我下水  我的"恩客满意度"有口皆碑
Speak for yourself. I've delivered.
说真的  麦克斯  那些有外送的
Seriously, Max, those delivery services--
外送网站  送餐软件  生意超大
Eat24, Grubhub-- do big business.
现在没人想出门了
No one wants to go out now.
大家都懒死了
People are so lazy.
我也懒得出去送
I don't really feel like it.
别闹了  麦克斯
Seriously, Max, all we have to do
我们只需要额外收个外送费
is slap a delivery charge on that product,
一个5块钱的小蛋糕会让我们数钱数到手抽筋
and suddenly, a $5 cupcake is bringing in more money.
你知道数钱数到手抽筋代表什么吗
And do you know what more money means?
我没经验  哪可能懂啊
No. How would I know that?
好了  提问
Okay, question:
哪件衣服比较配我裸下身
which of these goes better with no pants?
不知道  两件都是永恒款
I don't know. They're both timeless...
永恒没有适合场合穿的"永恒款"
As in, there's no time you should wear those.
你没法用客观眼光  你看到我就想扑上来
You can't be objective. You're like a kid in a candy store.
我要问麦克斯
I'll ask Max.
红色那件很搭你的红疹
Uh, well, the red one kind of matches your rash.
答案揭晓了
I think we have a winner.
为什么今晚要穿上你的网眼战袍呢
So why are you trying out the fancy mesh tonight?
虽然我跟苏菲重修旧好了
Well, even though Sophie and I are getting back together,
但我们想要把性爱的部分弄得特别点
we wanted to make it special and hold off on the sexual part
所以一直等到今晚才要圆房
of the relationship until tonight.
-好浪漫  -是啊
- That is so sweet. - I know.
我进来前刚打完飞机
I haven't even masturbated
一直忍到现在都没再打哦
since right before I came in here.
栗宝  我在杂货店买便宜卷纸的时候
So, Chestnut, I was buying some rolling papers at the bodega,
我怕丢人所以说是帮你买的  别生气啊
and I hope this is cool, but I said they were for you.
麦克斯  我有个好消息跟坏消息
Max, I have good news and bad news.
坏消息是
The bad news is,
这是我三年来唯一一件好消息
This is the only good news I've had in three years.
而好消息是...
And the good news is...
你找到新家要搬走了吗
You found yourself a new apartment?
臭女人  别让我白高兴啊
Don't toy with me, woman.
好好说  口齿清晰的说
Speak plainly and clearly.
你是不是找到新家要搬走了
Did you find a new apartment?
闭上眼睛  我给你个提示
Close your eyes. I'll give you a hint.
上一次别人让我闭上眼睛后
Last time I was told to close my eyes,
再睁开眼  发现自己穿着比基尼在垃圾船上
I woke up in a bikini on a garbage barge.
不过那是我此生最接近出海度假的一次了
P.S., closest I ever got to a vacation.
你的新男友是个小丑吗
Oh, you're dating a clown?
怎么可能  如果我有幸
Please, you know I would have told you
能跟有车一族约会  我早告诉你了
if I was dating someone who had a car.
你看  是店门口那台被人弃置的自行车
Look, it's the abandoned bike from in front of the shop.
它本来的确是店门口的自行车
It was the bike from the front of the shop.
现在则像是《鲁保罗变装自行车秀》的参赛者
Now it looks like a contestant on RuPaul's bike race.
我们要骑它去送外送
We're gonna use it to make deliveries.
我已经接了三个外送的单了
I already signed us up for three delivery services.
人穷依旧聪明如我
Still crazy smart.
浪费时间
Waste of time.
亚马逊都有无人飞机外送了
Amazon's got drones,
我们只有这台基爆的自行车
and we've got one gay bike.
我不想送外送
I don't want to do deliveries.
我来吧  你做小蛋糕  我送小蛋糕
I got this. You bake, I'll bike.
你送外卖去  我吸大麻去
And while you bike, I'll get baked.
我去把三个"送"全搞定了
I'm just gonna knock out these three "delivs"
然后就在店里跟你会合
and I'll met you at the cupcake shop.
-"送"是啥  -你喜欢"送"吗
- "Delivs"? - You like "delivs"?
是我给"外送"取的"短化叫"
It's an "abbreve" I made up for "deliveries."
你喜欢"短化叫"吗
You like "abbreve"?
是我给"短化叫法"取的"短叫"
It's an "ab" I made up for "abbreviation."
我也长话短说  滚
I'm gonna make this short. Get out.
大家安安
Hey, everybody.
苏菲  你觉得如何
Sophie, what do you think?
好事啊  卡洛琳
Aw, good for you, Caroline.
我早就建议你搞个"粉色的东西"骑
I've been saying that you should hop on something
你终于听我的话了
pink and ride it since I met you.
麦克斯  我就希望跟你独处
Ah, Max, I'm so glad you're alone,
因为我需要些"女孩谈话"
'cause I need some girl talk.
但上一次我跟人"女孩谈话"
Okay, but the last time I did girl talk,
首分钟收费3块钱
I got $3 for the first minute
之后每分钟1块钱呢
and $1 for each additional minute.
是跟奥列格有关的
No, it's about Oleg.
昨晚  他不能...
Last night, he was unable to...
我该怎么说得好听点呢
Oh, what's a nice way to say this?
他的小兵没有办法立正站好
He couldn't get his soldier to stand at attention,
然后他的鸡鸡也一直"垂头丧气"
and his penis wouldn't work either.
你试过去买一些
Well, uh, have you tried buying
女性杂志来读吗
a Cosmopolitan magazine or something?
里面通常有很多闺房建议
They usually have advice on sex stuff
以及如何痛恨自己身材的建议
and how to hate your body.
麦克斯
Max...
你不会觉得是因为我的关系吧
You don't think it could be me, do you?
怎么可能  苏菲  你辣到爆
No way, Sophie. You are hot.
奥列格第一次见你时
The first time Oleg saw you,
他的"小兵"不止"敬礼"了
His soldier not only saluted.
还"爆"了呢
It exploded.
你说得对  我魅力无法挡
You're right. I am hot.
全是他的问题
It's all him.
还记得我刚才说过不用你来送外卖吗
Remember when I said you didn't have to do deliveries?
你得来负责送外卖
You're gonna have to do deliveries,
因为我才骑个两个街区远
'cause I only went two blocks,
就跟希亚·拉博夫被抓酒驾时留一样多的汗了
and I'm sweating like Shia Lebeouf at a DUI checkpoint.
好吧  你外送  我来负责销售窗口
Okay, you deliver. I'll open the window.
但首先  开店宣誓
But first, business affirmation.
求你了  老天爷  别让我们被人拿枪敲到死
Please, God, don't let us get pistol-whipped in here.
不是滚娘干的就是蜘蛛侠出柜了
It's either that Guinevere or spider-man came out.
卡洛琳  我能跟你聊一件私事吗
Caroline, can I talk to you about a private matter,
私事就是指私处的事
by which I mean the matter is my privates.
好  快点说  奥列格
Okay, but hurry, Oleg.
我还得处理这"捕梦网"的事
I'm in the middle of a dream catcher situation,
真是捕了个大噩梦
and it's a nightmare.
而且为啥找我聊
And why me?
因为我相信你  也尊敬你
'Cause I trust and respect you
而且我觉得你对处理"软脚鸡"会很有一套
And I feel like you know your way around a limp penis.
可能吧
Maybe.
我跟我的心理医生说过了
I talked to my therapist--
罗伊  你懂的  那个星巴克店员
Roy, you know, down at the Starbucks.
他说这都是心理因素
He told me it's all mental.
但是我们没再深入探讨下去
We didn't get much further than that.
他打翻了一杯大杯咖啡到他拖鞋上
He spilled a grande mochaccino on his sandals.
你可能只是怯场
You're probably just scared.
亲密关系对某些男人很难
Intimacy is so hard for some guys,
也因此害他们很难硬
it's not hard for some guys.
是啊  这太难懂了
Yeah, that's all over my head.
麦克斯忘了拿外送单
Oh, no, Max forgot the order slips.
奥列格  我相信会水到渠成的
Oleg, I'm sure it'll all work out.
祝你的"通心粉"早日"软硬适中"
Good luck getting your penne al dente.
还是太难懂了
Again, over my head.
麦克斯  你在干嘛
Max, what are you doing?
你才在干嘛咧
What are you doing?
你说我在干嘛
What am I doing?
我在看着你把
Well, I think I'm watching you shove
我们的外送车塞进优步出租车里
our delivery bike into the back of an Uber car.
这下可超级[优步]尴尬了
Well, this is uber-awkward.
快点  坐就坐  不坐就走
Come on, come on. In or out.
卡洛琳  他叫米利旭  拼写有个不发音的K
All right, Caroline, this is Kmilesh, with a “k.”
他不去机场
He doesn't go to the airport,
他有一次载过五月天部分成员
and he once drove some of Maroon 5--
所以是三月天
so Maroon 3.
别这样  卡洛琳
No, stop. Caroline.
如果你想我去送小蛋糕
If you want me to deliver the cupcakes,
我不能骑车去  我得坐车去
I can't use the bike, I have to use the car.
为什么
Why?
天啊  你怀孕了吗
Oh, my God, are you pregnant?
你每天都问我  我也几乎每天说没有
You ask me that every day, and almost every day I say no.
我想告诉你  但这是个秘密
Look, I want to tell you, but it's a secret.
你不能告诉别人
And you can't tell anybody.
你真的觉得我会想跟任何人
Do you seriously think I would ever tell anyone
分享我这破生活的事吗
anything about this life?
好吧
Right.
我不知道怎么骑自行车
I don't know how to ride a bike, okay?
你不知道怎么骑自行车吗
You don't know how to ride a bike?
麦克斯不知道怎么骑自行车吗
Max doesn't know how to ride a bike?
我靠  卡洛琳
Damn it, Caroline!
麦克斯不知道怎么骑自行车
Max doesn't know how to ride a bike.
完美的一天啊
Oh, happy day.
我终于有强过她的事情了
I finally have something over her.
世上真有神
There is a God,
而他也正在笑麦克斯呢
and he's laughing at her too.
天啊  我看不下去了
Lordy, this is harder to watch
比看金·凯瑞演的剧情片还难
than Jim Carrey in a drama.
麦克斯  你没睡吧
Max, are you up?
怎么有股味儿  你打包了希腊菜回家吗
What's that smell? Did you bring home greek food?
没  那是我的味道
No, that's me.
我身上有这股味儿是因为我骑着自行车
That's how you smell after you ride a bike
跑遍整个威廉斯堡  送了14笔小蛋糕外卖
all over Williamsburg delivering 14 orders of cupcakes,
而我不希望身上再有这种味道了
And I do not wish to smell like this again,
所以你一定要学会骑自行车  知道吗
so you have to learn how to ride that bike, all right?
你以为你是谁啊
Who do you think you are
带着一股鹰嘴豆泥的味冲进来
busting in here smelling like hummus
却没带鹰嘴豆泥给我吃
but having no hummus?
到底是怎么回事
What is the problem?
你妈难道没教过你怎么骑自行车吗
Didn't your mother ever teach you how to ride a bike?
没有  我妈忙着当公共自行车被人"骑"呢
No, my mother was too busy being the town bike.
那好吧  我来教你
Well, then I'll teach you.
不要  绝不骑自行车
Nope. Never getting on a bike.
这是我"三绝师太"其中一条原则
It's one of my three "nevers."
是啊  你第一"绝"是
Yes, well, your first "never" was,
"绝不跟金发妞同住"
"Never having a blonde roommate."
小妞你一步一步似魔鬼般吞噬了我的原则啊
You are chipping away at me piece by piece, lady.
除非你告诉我原因  否则我哪儿也不去
I'm not going anywhere until you tell me what's going on.
我本来想坐你的床  但那是你的第三"绝"
I'd sit on your bed, but that's your third "never."
在我小的时候  有个孩子叫汤米·杜南
When I was little, there was this kid, Tommy Doonan.
人很乖  跳房子游戏界的一哥
Nice kid, solid hopscotcher.
每天午餐都会把他的水果卷给我
Used to give me his fruit roll-up at lunch every day.
麦克斯  水果卷是他给你的
Max, did he give you these fruit roll-ups,
还是你自己抢的
or did you take them?
别插嘴
Don't interrupt.
有一天  汤米·杜南买了一辆新的自行车
One day, Tommy Doonan got a new bike.
他跟一位跟他长得很像
He was out front with this nice,
很亲切的老男人出来玩
older man who looked just like him.
你是指他的爸爸吗
You mean his dad?
应该这么称呼那人吗
Mm, is that what they call them?
我还以为是叫恋童怪老头呢
I assumed it was a predator.
总而言之  我当时在嘲笑他
So anyway, I was making fun of him
因为他看起来很开心
'cause he seemed happy.
我还以为你只对我这样呢
I thought that was our thing.
然后他开始显摆特技  前轮离地之类的
And he started showing off, doing wheelies and stuff,
想挫挫我的锐气
to put me in my place,
结果他从车把后面飞出去
But then he flipped up over the handlebars
重重摔在地上  脸先着地哦
and came down hard on his face.
好可怜哦
Sad,
但不值得让我腋下骑出中东味儿
but not worth me having baklava pits.
还没说完呢
Well, wait.
我止住笑声后
After I stopped laughing
那男人把他扶起来  用恋童癖的方式拥抱他
and the man picked him up and hugged him predator-style,
我看见汤米的牙齿从脸颊冒出来
I saw Tommy's teeth had busted through his cheek.
说白了就是
To put it plainly,
他的嘴跑到他的脸外面了
his mouth was on the outside of his face.
感觉就是恐怖电影里的情节
Ew, that's like something out of a horror movie,
比如《自行车活死人》或《德州自行车链杀人狂》
like Bike of the Living Dead or Texas Bike Chain Massacre
还有...算了  说够了
Or--well, that's probably enough.